<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>사건사고</title>
    <link>http://gandol1028.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="/rss2.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    
    <description>It&#39;s a blog that deals with incidents all over the world.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 10:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    <generator>http://hexo.io/</generator>
    
    <item>
      <title>BLACKPINK &#39;SUMMER SONIC 2019&#39;Presentation! Expectations of performance in Japan&#39;s biggest music festival following full-scale promotion in the U.S.</title>
      <link>http://gandol1028.github.io/BLACKPINK/BLACKPINK-SUMMER-SONIC-2019-Presentation-Expectations-of-performance-in-Japan-s-biggest-music-festival-following-full-scale-promotion-in-the-U-S/</link>
      <guid>http://gandol1028.github.io/BLACKPINK/BLACKPINK-SUMMER-SONIC-2019-Presentation-Expectations-of-performance-in-Japan-s-biggest-music-festival-following-full-scale-promotion-in-the-U-S/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 10:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>
      
        
        
          &lt;p&gt;Popular K-POP girl group BLACKPINK has decided to star in the “SUMMER SONIC 2019,” which will be held at ZOZO Marine Stadium&amp;amp;Makuhari
        
      
      </description>
      
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Popular K-POP girl group BLACKPINK has decided to star in the “SUMMER SONIC 2019,” which will be held at ZOZO Marine Stadium&amp;Makuhari Maze, Chiba Prefecture, on August 18.<br>BLACKPINK debuted in Korea in 2016. All the songs released so far have been a smash hit, and the mini-album “SQUARE UP” released in June last year topped the itunes chart in 44 countries around the world. As of February this year, the music video for the title song “DU-DU DDU-DU” has surpassed 500 million replays on 162 days, recording a revival of over 660 million songs.</p><p>In 2017, she made her major debut in Japan, and her debut mini album “BLACKPINK” also topped the Oricon Weekly album chart. She’s famous for her new fashion icons, including “NYLON JAPAN,” “JJJ,” “GQ JAPAN” and “Numero Tokyo.” ABC Mart “PUMA SUEDE BOW” “CM” “CM” “CM” “CM” “CM.”</p><p>In addition, starting last summer, the Japanese tour “BLACKPINK AREA TOUR 2018” will be performed at Fukuoka International Center, Osaka Castle Hall, Makuhari Mossayevent Hall, and Kyoseradom Osaka, the “first in the history of overseas women’s groups.”For the first time, he ended his tour of 125,000 people for his first time in a three-city eight performance, and also made the name on a Japanese music scene.</p><p>The popularity now is not only in Korea or Japan, but BLACKPINK is the biggest music festival in Japan, which is receiving keen attention from all over the world as the only world class girl group. First to join SUMMER SONIC.</p><p>This year’s SUMMER SONIC 2019 will be announced on 8/16 (Gold), 8/17 (Toy), 8/18 (Day), Chiba Prefecture ZOZOmarin Stadium&amp;Makuhari Maze SONIC PARK (Mice Sports Island) and Osaka Department, for the first three days of the year, and will be held on Red Hot Chiliper Pez The Chest.</p><p>BLACKPINK’s hot performance with world-class artists is a must. We’ll be announcing it one after another on the site of SUMMER SONIC, so please pay attention to this as well.</p><p>In addition, they completed their participation in the largest music festival in the U.S. and Japan, not long after the announcement of their appearance in the world’s highest peak, largest outdoor Pace, “Cocera, Festival.”He is currently at the height of his world tour, and also signed with the prestigious American level, “Interscope Records.”</p><p>Starting with this year’s Grammy night event “Grami, Attist, Showcase” and completing his appearance on ABC’s flagship program “Good Morning America,” the Grammy Awards is finally starting.</p><p>“BLACKPINK AREA TOUR 2018, “SPECIAL FINAL IN KYOCERA DOME OSAKA,” which became the first foreign girl group to perform in Osaka at the end of last year, on March 13 (Su), is a live DVD&amp;Blu-ray program of the reality TV program “BLACKUE” that approaches their appeal.</p><h2 id="Summersonic-Tokyo-Performance-Overview"><a href="#Summersonic-Tokyo-Performance-Overview" class="headerlink" title="Summersonic Tokyo Performance Overview"></a>Summersonic Tokyo Performance Overview</h2><p>SUMMMER SONIC 2019 (Summersonic Nissenjoucu/Tusaujandnainatin)<br>Calendar:August 16, 2010/17 (Today)/18 (Day)<br>Performance Hall: ZOZO Marine Stadium &amp; Makuhari Masse<br>Open/Open:Open AM 9:00 / Open AM 11:00<br>Ticket date: May 25th AM10:00~</p><p>MOFFICIAL PARTNERRS<br>OFFICIAL MEDIA:J-WAVE / InterFM897 / bayfm<br>MEDIA PARTNERS: SPACE SHOWER TV<br>Planning, Fabrication and Invitation: Creative Man</p><p>Phosphorus<br>OFFICIAL SITE: <a href="http://www.summersonic.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.summersonic.com</a><br>OFFICIAL TWITTER: <a href="http://twitter.com/summer_sonic" target="_blank" rel="noopener">http://twitter.com/summer_sonic</a><br>OFFICIAL FACEBOOK: <a href="http://www.facebook.com/summersonicfestival" target="_blank" rel="noopener">http://www.facebook.com/summersonicfestival</a><br>OFFICIAL FACEBOOK: <a href="http://www.facebook.com/summersonicfestival" target="_blank" rel="noopener">http://www.facebook.com/summersonicfestival</a></p><h2 id="Somersonic"><a href="#Somersonic" class="headerlink" title="Somersonic."></a>Somersonic.</h2><p>“SUMMER SONIC (SAM SONIC),” a city-style festival in August 2000.<br>Korea’s first holding and staging artists in two major cities in<br>Gwandong and Kansai, under a groundbreaking fashion called<br>“Comprehensive Body,” “Green Day” and “Bruce Exhibition” are<br>gathered as headliner and started by domestic and foreign artists.</p><p>After that, the musical industry’s “incident,” including the legendary band, Gance and Rosy’s, was shocked and many audienes felt. Line-up, which is envied by overseas courses such as Radio Head, Bla, Oasis, Metallica, Linkin Park, Daft Funk, Massive Attack, and so on, is the talk of the town every year. In 2007, it became the talk of the headliner.</p><p>By the end of the decade, the world’s top-ranked artists such as Ariana and Grande, Lady Gaga, Farrell, Queen+Adams and Lumbert will also come to Japan.</p><p>In addition, the new cast of Coldplay, Cigar Ross, Muse and The Stroke returned to the headliner-level act a few years later, which is a major feature of Samasoni.</p><p>In recent years, the first of its kind to open the Sangha in Samasoni, has grown to be not only a music fan in Asia but also a big draw around the world. In 2019, Samasoni, which celebrates its 20th anniversary, decided to hold the event for three days.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      
      <comments>http://gandol1028.github.io/BLACKPINK/BLACKPINK-SUMMER-SONIC-2019-Presentation-Expectations-of-performance-in-Japan-s-biggest-music-festival-following-full-scale-promotion-in-the-U-S/#disqus_thread</comments>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTS&#39;s V has the Grammy&#39;s eye! &#39;That green-haired man is hot.&#39;</title>
      <link>http://gandol1028.github.io/BTS/BTS-s-V-has-the-Grammy-s-eye-That-green-haired-man-is-hot/</link>
      <guid>http://gandol1028.github.io/BTS/BTS-s-V-has-the-Grammy-s-eye-That-green-haired-man-is-hot/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 09:55:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>
      
        
        
          &lt;p&gt;BTS (Bangtan Youth Corps) participated in the Grammy Awards and received attention from global viewers and the media, but V seems to have
        
      
      </description>
      
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTS (Bangtan Youth Corps) participated in the Grammy Awards and received attention from global viewers and the media, but V seems to have received a lot of attention.</p><p>On February 10 (local time), the Grammy Awards ceremony was held in Los Angeles, the biggest music award ceremony in the U.S.BTS (Bangtan Youth Corps), a Korean popular hip-hop group, appeared as a presenter at the awards ceremony, and became the first Korean writer to play a big role, drawing attention from all over the world.</p><p>However, V (Kim Tae-hyun), a member of the BTS, seems to have received attention for another reason.</p><p>V appeared at the awards ceremony with mint green hair.</p><p>Okay, I’m watching Grammy right now. I’m not a fan of BTS, but the guy with the green hair… Who’s this beautiful?</p><div class="twitter-wrapper"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><a href="https://twitter.com/MTV/status/1094755188265631744" target="_blank" rel="noopener"></a></blockquote></div><script async defer src="//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script><p>Who has green hair?Spitting a lot of energy, Grammy looks like his show.</p><p>“He’s very sunny. Especially that guy with green hair!”</p><p>I don’t know anything about K-pop, but teach me how to wear glasses and him with green hair!We need to know who it is,” said a comment, which seems to be the talk of V’s appeal.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      
      <comments>http://gandol1028.github.io/BTS/BTS-s-V-has-the-Grammy-s-eye-That-green-haired-man-is-hot/#disqus_thread</comments>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTS fans are going to challenge the world leader in Twitter! BTS Celebrations for Historical Revelation</title>
      <link>http://gandol1028.github.io/BTS/BTS-fans-are-going-to-challenge-the-world-leader-in-Twitter-BTS-Celebrations-for-Historical-Revelation/</link>
      <guid>http://gandol1028.github.io/BTS/BTS-fans-are-going-to-challenge-the-world-leader-in-Twitter-BTS-Celebrations-for-Historical-Revelation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 09:53:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>
      
        
        
          &lt;p&gt;Popular K-pop boy band BTS (Bangtan Youth Corps) attended the Grammy Awards ceremony for the first time as a Korean writer on February 10
        
      
      </description>
      
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Popular K-pop boy band BTS (Bangtan Youth Corps) attended the Grammy Awards ceremony for the first time as a Korean writer on February 10 in the U.S. time.</p><p>BTS’s fans are in a big trouble because of its historic success. A big project was launched to please a member of the BTS (Bangtan Youth Corps) who made this wonderful event happen, which is also proud.</p><p>The U.S. government aims to achieve the world record by celebrating the attendance of BTS at the Grammy Awards.</p><p>Specifically, it is a challenge for fans to achieve the world record for hashtag, which is the most widely used hashtag in 24 hours, by making contributions with hashtag #Tear ItUpBTS.</p><p>The record has been used the most in charity performances in the Philippines so far. In the tag #Al DubEBTamang Panahon, more than 40 million tweets were submitted on October 24, 2015.</p><p>The challenge by BTS fans is seen as a good chance of breaking the record. Joining the worldwide popularity of BTS, the challenge was because there was a video clip that explains how to tweet.</p><p>According to a fan, three hours after the start, 20 million Ingements (such as “OK!” “Construction,” “Share” and “Click” are recorded) are now being recorded, which seems to be a smooth transition.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      
      <comments>http://gandol1028.github.io/BTS/BTS-fans-are-going-to-challenge-the-world-leader-in-Twitter-BTS-Celebrations-for-Historical-Revelation/#disqus_thread</comments>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At the end of BTS, tears at the Grammy Awards! Are you impressed by the stage of your dreams?</title>
      <link>http://gandol1028.github.io/BTS/At-the-end-of-BTS-tears-at-the-Grammy-Awards-Are-you-impressed-by-the-stage-of-your-dreams/</link>
      <guid>http://gandol1028.github.io/BTS/At-the-end-of-BTS-tears-at-the-Grammy-Awards-Are-you-impressed-by-the-stage-of-your-dreams/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 09:52:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>
      
        
        
          &lt;p&gt;BTS (Bangtan Youth Corps) is attending the Grammy Awards. Members seem very pleased to have been able to participate in the grand event t
        
      
      </description>
      
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTS (Bangtan Youth Corps) is attending the Grammy Awards. Members seem very pleased to have been able to participate in the grand event that the world is paying attention to, but most of all, they seem to be moving too much to see the performances of luxury artists in front of their eyes.</p><p>The 61st Grammy Awards was held at Staples Center in Los Angeles on February 10 and was the first Korean artist to play a presenter at the awards ceremony.</p><p>A member of BTS, in the artist’s waiting room until his turn, watches the show.When popular singers Miley Silas and Dolly Parton performed their special duet of the hit song “Jolene,” BTS members were able to enjoy their oars to the music.</p><p>Then Marie Silas and Dr. Parton made a beautiful chord known to the event, covering Neil Young’s After the Gold Rush.The youngest member of the BTS, Jong-guk, was moved by the performance of the two.Other members who realized that they were crying are smiling a little.</p><p>Realizing that the end is crying, fans are tears of great happiness.I’m glad too. I’m so glad the BTS members are really enjoying it.</p><p>“Hahaha, you guys are funny. Cute.”</p><p>I’m crying, too.I love you.</p><p>I’m sure you’ll be proud of this wonderful experience.I’m glad I could have a great time,” and so on, “and so on, and so on, there’s a lot of blessing on the members of BTS who have reached the stage of their dreams.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      
      <comments>http://gandol1028.github.io/BTS/At-the-end-of-BTS-tears-at-the-Grammy-Awards-Are-you-impressed-by-the-stage-of-your-dreams/#disqus_thread</comments>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In the end of BTS (Bangtan Youth Corps), Grammy&#39;s actions are praised as super-human.</title>
      <link>http://gandol1028.github.io/BTS/In-the-end-of-BTS-Bangtan-Youth-Corps-Grammy-s-actions-are-praised-as-super-human/</link>
      <guid>http://gandol1028.github.io/BTS/In-the-end-of-BTS-Bangtan-Youth-Corps-Grammy-s-actions-are-praised-as-super-human/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 09:46:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>
      
        
        
          &lt;p&gt;The youngest member of BTS is praised as a super gentleman.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Local time on February 10th, Korean pop group BTS (Bangtan Boys’ Club)
        
      
      </description>
      
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The youngest member of BTS is praised as a super gentleman.</p><p>Local time on February 10th, Korean pop group BTS (Bangtan Boys’ Club) attended the U.S. highest-class music award ceremony called “The Grammy Award Ceremony.”</p><p>BTS members are also famous for idol singers who do not forget their modesty and manners.</p><p>The BTS member was reunited with Lily Singh, who played as a Canadian actress/You Tube star in the Grammy Awards. BTS and Lily Singh met at the 2017 American Music Awards and are reuniting in 2018, when BTS attended the U.N. General Assembly.</p><h2 id="an-end-of-life-spending"><a href="#an-end-of-life-spending" class="headerlink" title="an end-of-life spending"></a>an end-of-life spending</h2><p>At the Grammy Awards, BTS RM and J-Hope, who met Lily Singh again, took a commemorative photo with her and posted it on their official Twitter page.</p><p>Although it seems like a regular group shot, BTS fans seem to have finally realized their tender consideration.</p><p>The end is reaching toward the RM so that his hand does not touch Lily Singh’s shoulder directly and placing his hand on his shoulder.BTS fans praise this woman for her caring behavior as very</p><p>In the end, he is resting his hand on the shoulders of South China.He is always pretty, modest, and polite.</p><p>Eventually, he is the cutest person in the world.This is our country! Everyone! It’s so full of respect.All of the members are like that way!I can’t tell you how much I like this picture with them. OMG Lily! It’s too much of a go-getter.</p><h2 id="When-I-met-Holsey"><a href="#When-I-met-Holsey" class="headerlink" title="When I met Holsey,"></a>When I met Holsey,</h2><p>In the end, when he met singer Holji at the Billboard Music Awards, he took pictures with her shoulder, and he was careful not to touch her hand, which made him the subject of loving behavior.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      
      <comments>http://gandol1028.github.io/BTS/In-the-end-of-BTS-Bangtan-Youth-Corps-Grammy-s-actions-are-praised-as-super-human/#disqus_thread</comments>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>승리 버닝썬 폭행사건</title>
      <link>http://gandol1028.github.io/celebrity/victoryburningsun/</link>
      <guid>http://gandol1028.github.io/celebrity/victoryburningsun/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 05:46:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>
      
        
        
          &lt;p&gt;클럽 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;버닝썬&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;에서 마약 유통책으로 활동했다는 의혹을 받은 중국인 여자분이 빅뱅 빅뱅의 승리와 함께찍은 사진과 동영상이 다수 공개됐습니다. 이 여자분은 자신의 SNS에서 자신이 클럽 버닝썬에서 일한다고도
        
      
      </description>
      
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>클럽 <strong><em>버닝썬</em></strong>에서 마약 유통책으로 활동했다는 의혹을 받은 중국인 여자분이 빅뱅 빅뱅의 승리와 함께찍은 사진과 동영상이 다수 공개됐습니다. 이 여자분은 자신의 SNS에서 자신이 클럽 버닝썬에서 일한다고도 밝혀 파문이 일어났습니다.</p><p><img src="K-009.jpg" alt="버닝썬 CCTV 1"></p><p>지난 십삼일 자신이 지난해 십일월 발생한 <strong><em>버닝썬 폭력 사건</em></strong> 피해자라고 주장 중인 김모씨는 자신의 SNS에 빅뱅의 승리와 중국인 여자분 <strong><em>애나</em></strong>가 함께 찍은 동영상 캡처사진을 게재했습니다. </p><p>자신의 닉네임을 <strong><em>애나</em></strong>로 밝힌 이 여자분은 지난해 10월 빅뱅의 승리와 함께 클럽 버닝썬에서 찍은 것으로 추정되는 동영상을 자신의 SNS에 게재했는데,<br>사진과 함께 게재한 글에는 </p><blockquote><p>“열심히 일해야 빅뱅의 승리 대표와 사진을 찍지. 이번 주 취했다가 열일”</p></blockquote><p>이라면서 빅뱅의 승리를 버닝썬의 대표라고 언급하고 있습니다.</p><p><strong><em>애나</em></strong>는 앞서 버닝썬 내에서 마약류인 알약 공급책으로 활동하는 동시에 MD로 일하며 버닝썬에 중국계 손님들을 유치하는 일을 해왔다고 알려 지고있습니다. </p><p>이외 에도 일부 언론매체의 보도에 따르면 김 씨를 클럽 내 성추행으로 고소한 여자분 2명 중 한 명이 <strong><em>애나</em></strong>였던 것으로 전해졌죠. </p><p>김 씨는 버닝썬 측이 클럽 내 마약 유통에 대해 부인한 것을 꼬집는 의도로 이 사진을 게재한 것으로 보여집니다. 이 사진은 현재 지워졌습니다.</p><p><img src="K-010.jpg" alt="버닝썬 CCTV 2"></p><p>MBC <strong><em>뉴스데스크</em></strong> 보도에 따르면 <strong><em>애나</em></strong>는 중국 국적의 여상 파모씨로 8년 전 서울의 한 대학 연기학과에 외국인 전형으로 입학해 지난해 졸업했습니다. </p><p>같은 해 대마초 혐의로 기소유예 처분을 받은 이력도 있으며, 현재 여권이 만료돼 불법체류 상태인 것으로 전해 지고있습니다. </p><p>경찰은 십삼일 <strong><em>애나</em></strong>를 조사할 계획이지만 아직까지 이 여자분과 연락이 닿고 있지 않다고 밝혔죠.</p><p>앞서 버닝썬 대표에서 사임한 빅뱅의 승리 또한 <strong><em>애나</em></strong>와의 친분을 부인했습니다.<br>이 동영상에 관해 빅뱅의 승리는 </p><blockquote><p>“클럽에 있다가, 함께 사진을 찍어달라고 하시기에 찍어드린 것”</p></blockquote><blockquote><p>“사진을 찍은 시점이 정확하게 언제인지, 저 분이 어떤 분인지 잘 기억이 나질 않을 정도”</p></blockquote><p>라고 친분을 부인 했습니다.</p><p><img src="K-011.jpg" alt="버닝썬 CCTV 3"></p><p>하지만 빅뱅의 승리에게 도의적 책임은 여전히 존재한다는 의견이 대세입니다. 앞서 빅뱅의 승리 측은 버닝썬 폭력, 성추행, 마약 유통 논란에 관해</p><blockquote><p>“실제 운영에는 관여하지 않았다”</p></blockquote><p>라고 밝힌 바 있습니다.그러나 MBC <strong><em>나 혼자 산다</em></strong>등을 통해 자신이 직접 클럽을 운영한다고 강조하고, 이를 통해 클럽 홍보에 일조한 것은 분명한 사실입니다. 대중들은 이에 관해</p><blockquote><p>“연예인이 자신의 이름을 내걸고 지상파 방송 속에서 대대적으로 홍보했으니 안심하고 클럽에 갔다가 피해를 본 사람도 있을 것”</p></blockquote><p>이라며 </p><blockquote><p>“클럽의 유명세에 일조한 이상 빅뱅의 승리가 도의적으로 책임져야 하는 부분은 분명 있다”</p></blockquote><p>고 지적했습니다.</p><p>이제 와서 </p><blockquote><p>“운영에는 관여하지 않았다”</p></blockquote><blockquote><p>“친분이 없는 사람” </p></blockquote><p>등의 변명으로 일관하는 모습이 실망스럽습니다.</p><p>분명 운영하지 않았을 수 있습니다. <strong><em>애나</em></strong>도 모르는 사람일 수 있습니다. </p><p>하지만 그가 돈을 투자하고, 빅뱅의 승리의 어머니가 감사로 재직했고, 직원들이 빅뱅의 승리를 대표라고 불렀으며 빅뱅의 승리 자신이 방송에서 실제로 운영하고 있다고 말한 것은 사실입니다.<br>그렇다면 빅뱅의 승리의 태도에 대중들이 실망하는 것도 감수해야 하지 않을까요.<br>그가 속한 그룹 빅뱅의 히트곡 <strong><em>루저</em></strong> 가사 속 <strong><em>센척하는 겁쟁이, 못된 양아치</em></strong>라는 부분이 유난히 씁쓸하게 맴돕니다. </p>]]></content:encoded>
      
      <comments>http://gandol1028.github.io/celebrity/victoryburningsun/#disqus_thread</comments>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
